Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- dbqp Records, 1982; 1987-2006; 4; 2.5 cubic ft.
  - dbqp Publications, 1982; 1987-2005; 4.1; 1 cubic ft.
    - dbqp #89, Hood, Wharton, warm drizzle, 15 April 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 90)
    - dbqp #90, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #32: Borderblur, 30 April 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 91)
    - dbqp #91, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #7, 10 May 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 92)
    - dbqp #92, Huth, G., The Russian Book of The, 25 May 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 93)
    - dbqp #93, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #33: Extrsuper hippopotomonstrosesquipedalianisms, 31 May 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 94)
    - dbqp #94, Brock, Randall, i am, 5 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 95)
    - dbqp #95, curry, jw and MBDuggan, 2/2, 10 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 96)
    - dbqp #96, Kempton, Karl and Jonathan Brannen, The Pluraled, 15 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 97)
    - dbqp #97, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #34: Anglovenezolismos, 30 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 98)
    - dbqp #98, dbqprodbooqpdb #5: Last Catalog at the Book Burning, 15 July 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 99)
    - dbqp #99, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #35: Pneumathink, 31 July 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 100)
    - dbqp #100, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #36: Isosyn, 1 August 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 101)
    - dbqp #101, dbqp #101: An Introduction to the History and data base of dbqp, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 102)
    - dbqp #102, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #8, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 103)
    - dbqp #103, Epistulational Exscrapts #3: a fuse, friends, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 104)
    - dbqp #104, Socks, Dregs and Rocking Chairs #3, by J. Ryan, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 105)
    - dbqp #105, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #37: Huvelma, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 106)
    - dbqp #106, ovingm #3, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 107)
    - dbqp #107, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #38: Moroccasins, 31 October 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 108)
    - dbqp #108, Huth, Geoffrey A., A Finger of Speech, 30 November 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 109)
    - dbqp #109, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #39: Coplicate, 30 November 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 110)
    - dbqp #110, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #3, 28 December 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 111)
    - dbqp #111, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #40: Exireries, 31 December 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 112)
    - dbqp #112, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #41: Mericasan, 1 January 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 113)
    - dbqp #113, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #42: Nightmarriage, 2 February 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 114)
    - dbqp #114, Huth, G., the leevs, 24 February 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 115)
    - dbqp #115, Richman, Elliot, The White light shatters, 12 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 116)
    - dbqp #116, A Voice Without Sides #5, 15 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 117)
    - dbqp #117, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #43: Gnowing, 23 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 118)
    - dbqp #118, Socks, Dregs and Rocking Chairs #4, Matt Towler and Doug Chapel, Mindflow, 28 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 119)
    - dbqp #119, Brannen, Jonathan, Sirloin Clouds, 31 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 120)
    - dbqp #120, Hill, Crag, Reading his Margin, 1 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 121)
    - dbqp #121, Praecisio Press Project Profile #2, 3 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 122)
    - dbqp #122, dbqprodbooqpdb #6: Catalog Intermadia Res, 5 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 123)
    - dbqp #123, Ryan, J., MOON, 10 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 124)
    - dbqp #124, ovingm #4, 11 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 125)
    - dbqp #125, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #10, 25 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 126)
    - dbqp #126, Bennett, John M., span, 26 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 127)
    - dbqp #127, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #44: Scaruscatracery, 30 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 128)
    - dbqp #128, Kostelauetz, Richard, Uninflected, Nonsyntactic Prose, 1 May 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 129)
    - dbqp #129, Janice, Karl, up/dn, 5 May 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 130)
    - dbqp #130, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #45: Pegue, 30 May 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 131)
    - dbqp #131, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #46: Serendipity, 30 June 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 132)
    - dbqp #132, Huth, G., bo, ok of unLloYdb, 5 July 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 133)
    - dbqp #133, Huth, G., th shlls, 26 July 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 134)
    - dbqp #134, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #47: Nayms, 30 July 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 135)
    - dbqp #135, Brannen, Jonathan, e.g. no p.s., 1 August 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 136)
    - dbqp #136, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #48: Synchroneologisms, 30 August 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 137)
    - dbqp #137, dbqprodbooqpdb #7: Catalog ex Instremis, 14 September 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 138)
    - dbqp #138, Swede, George, nightfallselvesalmostfuseintone, 20 September 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 139)
    - dbqp #139, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #49: Eternaphemera, 30 September 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 140)
    - dbqp #140, Buried Tongue, first incarnation: Duchamp, 2 October 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 141)
    - dbqp #141, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #50: Flossary, 31 October 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 142)
    - dbqp #142, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #51: Temorage, 30 November 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 143)
    - dbqp #143, barnes, r., our medicine was, 30 December 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 144)
    - dbqp #144, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #52: mailstrom, 31 December 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 145)
    - dbqp #145, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #1: Anotherwards, Second Edition, 18 January 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 146)
    - dbqp #146, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #11, 25 January 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 147)
    - dbqp #147, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #53: Volumn, 31 January 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 148)
    - dbqp #148, Brannen, Jonathan, Birth, Copulation and Death, 2 February 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 149)
    - dbqp #149, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #54: Excestuous, 29 February 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 150)
    - dbqp #150, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #55: Alterior, 31 March 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 151)
    - dbqp #151, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #56: Lifegear, 30 April 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 152)
    - dbqp #152, Helsem, Michael, Lifegear, 1 May 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 153)
    - dbqp #153, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #57: Opposets, 31 May 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 154)
    - dbqp #154, Huth, G., b, 15 June 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 155)
    - dbqp #155, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #58: Dorpian, 30 June 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 156)
    - dbqp #156, Huth, G., A number of space, 25 July 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 157)
    - dbqp #157, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #59: Vril, 31 July 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 158)
    - dbqp #158, dbqprodbooqpdb #8: In Statis Catalog In Perpetuity, 2 August 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 159)
    - dbqp #159, Huth, G. and afungusboy, A Disease of Carcass Awaiting, 1992 August (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 160)
    - dbqp #160, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #12, 9 August 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 161)
    - dbqp #161, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #60: Unnon, 3 August 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 162)
    - dbqp #162, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #61: Pyrotorriflavttential, 30 September 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 163)
    - dbqp #163, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #62: stramge speace, 31 October 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 164)
    - dbqp #164, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #63: Politricks, 3 November 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 165)
    - dbqp #165, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #13, 15 December 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 166)
    - dbqp #166, A Voice Without Sides #6, 16 December 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 167)
    - dbqp #167, Huth, G., O, 24 December 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 168)
    - dbqp #168, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #64: Verbier Lettre Documentaire XX, New Series, 31 December 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 169)
    - dbqp #169, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #65: Wrongsense, 31 January 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 170)
    - dbqp #170, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #66: Japanease, 28 February 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 171)
    - dbqp #171, Kopaska-Merkel, David C., A Round White Hole, 21 March 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 172)
    - dbqp #172, Grumman, Bob, Mathemaku for Ronald Johnson, 28 March 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 173)
    - dbqp #173, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #67: di-con-vergent, 31 March 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 174)
    - dbqp #174, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #68: bascyau, 30 April 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 175)
    - dbqp #175, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #69: Contemporary Reworkings, 31 May 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 176)
    - dbqp #176, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #70: synchrodipity, 30 June 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 177)
    - dbqp #177, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #71: wongi, 31 July 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 178)
    - dbqp #178, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #72: torchurch, 31 August 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 179)
    - dbqp #179, ovingm #5, 27 September 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 180)
    - dbqp #180, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #73: yetc., 30 September 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 181)
    - dbqp #181, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #74: fepresstle, 31 October 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 182)
    - dbqp #182, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #75: bokanovskification, 30 November 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 183)
    - dbqp #183, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #76: imedge, 31 December 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 184)
    - dbqp #184, Ge(of Huth), po.ed.t, business card, 18 January 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 185)
    - dbqp #185, dbqprodbooqpdb #8: of one catalog eternaphemeral, be it, 30 January 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 186)
    - dbqp #186, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #77: trashion, 31 January 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 187)
    - dbqp #187, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #78: contratradition, 28 February 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 188)
    - dbqp #188, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #79: gainrising, 31 March 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 189)
    - dbqp #189, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #80: foreignation, 30 April 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 190)
    - dbqp #190, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #14, 30 May 1994 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 191)
    - dbqp #191, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #15, 5 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 192)
    - dbqp #192, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #81: viewe, 13 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 193)
    - dbqp #193, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #82: cyburbs, 14 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 194)
    - dbqp #194, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #83: yby, 15 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 195)
    - dbqp #195, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #83: clumbjoe, 16 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 196)
    - dbqp #196, Lucero, Anthony, Out, 16 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 197)
    - dbqp #197, Foolscap #1: putting my clubfoot in my mouth again, 16 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 198)
    - dbqp #198, Scannell, Tim, 3 poemettes, 17 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 199)
    - dbqp #199, Rutter, Mark, Alphabets, 20 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 200)
    - dbqp #200, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #85: Anthopteron, 20 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 201)
    - dbqp #201, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #86: Islamdancing, 26 March 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 202)
    - dbqp #202, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #87: Paradachshund, 16 June 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 203)
    - dbqp #203, Grumman, Bob, 2 poems, 21 July 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 204)
    - dbqp #204, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #88: Gjefk, 29 July 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 205)
    - dbqp #205, Grumman, Bob, Of Poem, 13 October 1995 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 206)
    - dbqp #206, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #89: An Atomy, 6 October 2000 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 207)
    - dbqp #207, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #90: Kidspeak, 6 October 2000 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 208)
    - dbqp #208, ge(of Huth)/dbqp/geof Huth/pdqb, business card, 18 May 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 209)
    - dbqp #209, Huth, G., birchth, 11 October 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 210)
    - dbqp #210, Foolscap #2: endwords, 16 October 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 211)
    - dbqp #211, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #91: finjer, 31 October 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 212)
    - dbqp #212, Huth, G., vision: exterpreting the phaistos disk, 22 November 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 213)
    - dbqp #213, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #92: harumphrodite, 30 November 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 214)
    - dbqp #214, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #93: eucatastrophe, 30 December 2002 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 215)
    - dbqp #215, Foolscap #3: Of Poetry and Speech and Print, 10 January 2003 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 216)
    - dbqp #216, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #94: perhapsody, 31 January 2003 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 217)
    - dbqp #217, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #95: Prevenge, 16 February 2003 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 218)
    - dbqp #218, Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #16, 29 March 2003 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 219)
    - dbqp #219, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #96: Incumbocrat, 31 March 2003 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 220)
    - dbqp #220, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #97: Wordganism, 30 April 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 221)
    - dbqp #221, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #98: Psychedelinquent, 31 May 2003 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 222)
    - dbqp #222, Topel, Andrew, Signs of Language, 4 July 2004 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 223)
    - dbqp #223, Chikhladze, David, three green tea, 29 August 2004 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 224)
    - dbqp #224, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #99: Retoonric, Blue Cover, 31 August 2004 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 225)
    - dbqp #224, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #99: Retoonric, Pink Cover, 31 August 2004 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 226)
    - dbqp #224, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #99: Retoonric, Red Cover, 31 August 2004 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 227)
    - dbqp #224, The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #99: Retoonric, Yellow Cover, 31 August 2004 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 228)
    - dbqp #225, Huth, Geof, water vapour, 2005 December (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 229)
  - dbqp Layouts to Publications, 1987-2005; 4.2; 0.75 cubic ft.
    Includes layout copies of many dbqp publications and copies of manuscripts used in producing the issues.
    - dbqp #15: G. Huth, "ONCE UPON ANY TIME THERE WAS", 4 December 1987 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 1)
    - dbqp #18: dbqprodbooqpdb #1, 2 January 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 2)
    - dbqp #20: Strawberry Saroyan, "S E C O N D S", 20 January 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 3)
    - dbqp #21: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #1, 30 January 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 4)
    - dbqp #24: Greg Evason, "pierce thru teams and lines of that", 24 February 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 5)
    - dbqp #25: Praecisio Press Project Profile #1, 27 February 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 6)
    - dbqp #26: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #6, 29 February 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 7)
    - dbqp #26: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #6: Labrys, 29 February 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 8)
    - dbqp #27: Vince Lisella, "Propaganda in Hell", February 1988; 3 March 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 9)
    - dbqp #28: Karl Kempton, "lemniscates cape: ribbons in the wind", 8 March 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 10)
    - dbqp #33: ovingm #1, 20 May 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 11)
    - dbqp #34: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #9, 24 May 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 12)
    - dbqp #35: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #2, 25 May 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 13)
    - dbqp #36: Epistulational Exscrapts, 31 May 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 14)
    - dbqp #38: dbqprodbooqpdb #2, 27 June 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 15)
    - dbqp # 39: Karl Kempton, "doubt", 30 June 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 16)
    - dbqp #41: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #3, 30 July 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 17)
    - dbqp #47: John M. Bennett, "Snails", 15 October 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 18)
    - dbqp #52: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #16, 31 December 1988 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 19)
    - dbqp #55: dbqprodbooqpdb #3, 12 February 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 20)
    - dbqp #56: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #18, 22 February 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 21)
    - dbqp #57: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #4, 28 February 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 22)
    - dbqp #58: A Voice Without Sides #3, 23 March 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 23)
    - dbqp #61: Socks, Dregs and Rocking Chairs #2, 14 April 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 24)
    - dbqp #71: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #24, 30 August 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 25)
    - dbqp #73: Guy R. Beining, "Len", 15 October 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 26)
    - dbqp #74: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #26, 31 October 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 27)
    - dbqp #75: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #5, 10 November 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 28)
    - dbqp #76: dbqprodbooqpdb #4, 18 November 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 29)
    - dbqp #79: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #6, 10 December 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 30)
    - dbqp #80: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #28, 31 December 1989 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 31)
    - dbqp #83: Greg Evason and Daniel F. Bradley, Satan's World, 3 February 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 32)
    - dbqp #85: Epistulational Exscrapts #2, 10 March 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 33)
    - dbqp #86: John M. Bennett, "Tombescence", 12 March 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 34)
    - dbqp #87: David C. Kopaska-Merkel, "echo", 29 March 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 35)
    - dbqp #91: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #7, 10 May 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 36)
    - dbqp #93: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage # 33, 31 May 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 37)
    - dbqp #94: Randall Brock, " i am", 5 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 38)
    - dbqp #95: jwcurry/MBDuggan, 212, 10 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 39)
    - dbqp #96: Karl Kempton and Jonathan Brannen, "The Pluraled", 15 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 40)
    - dbqp #97: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage # 34, 30 June 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 41)
    - dbqp #98: dbqprodbooqpdb #5: Last Catalog at the Book Burning, 15 July 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 42)
    - dbqp #101: dbqp #101: An Introduction to the History and Data Base of dbqp, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 43)
    - dbqp #102: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #8, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 44)
    - dbqp #104: Socks, Dregs and Rocking Chairs #3, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 45)
    - dbqp #105: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #37, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 46)
    - dbqp #106: ovingm #3, 30 September 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 47)
    - dbqp #107: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #38, 31 October 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 48)
    - dbqp #109: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #39, 30 November 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 49)
    - dbqp #110: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #9, 28 December 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 50)
    - dbqp #111: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #40, 31 December 1990 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 51)
    - dbqp #112: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #41, 1 January 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 52)
    - dbqp #113: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #42, 2 February 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 53)
    - dbqp #114: G. Huth, the leevs, 24 February 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 54)
    - dbqp #117: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #43, 23 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 55)
    - dbqp #118: Socks, Dregs and Rocking Chairs #4: Matt Towler and Doug Chapel, Mindflow, 28 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 56)
    - dbqp #119: Jonathan Brannen, Sirloin Cloud, 31 March 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 57)
    - dbqp #120: Crag Hill, Reading his margin, 1 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 58)
    - dbqp #121: Praecisio Press Project Profile #2, 3 April 1993 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 59)
    - dbqp #122: dbqprodbooqpdb #6: Catalog Intermedia Res, 5 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 60)
    - dbqp #124: ovingm #4, 11 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 61)
    - dbqp #125: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #10, 20 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 62)
    - dbqp #126: Bennett, John M., "span", 26 April 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 63)
    - dbqp #128: Richard Kostelanetz, Uninflected, Nonsyntactic Prose, 1 May 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 64)
    - dbqp #129: Karl Janice, "up/dn", 5 May 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 65)
    - dbqp #136: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #48: Syachroneologisius, 30 August 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 66)
    - dbqp #137: dbqprodbooqpdb: Catalog Ex Intremis, 14 September 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 67)
    - dbqp #138: George Swede, "nightfallselvesalmostfuseintone", 20 September 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 68)
    - dbqp #139: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #49: Eternaphemera, 30 September 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 69)
    - dbqp #140: Buried Tongue, first incarnation: Duchamp, 2 October 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 70)
    - dbqp #141: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage: #50: Flossary, 31 October 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 71)
    - dbqp #144: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #52: mailstrom, 31 December 1991 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 72)
    - dbqp #145: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #1: Anotherwards, 8 January 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 73)
    - dbqp #146: Alabama Dogshoe Moustache #11, 25 January 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 74)
    - dbqp #147: The Subtle Journal of Raw Coinage #53: Volumn, 31 January 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 75)
    - dbqp #148: Jonathan Brannen, "Birth, Copulation, Death", 2 February 1992 (Box 1 (4-dbqp Records), Folder 76)